

KHOI NGUYEN

WEB & MOBILE DEVELOPER

PROFILE

IT Student at NBCC with 2 years of studying front-end and back-end web development. Potential experience of web and mobile development skills. Seeking opportunities to contribute knowledge to build products for users and achieve the dream of being a web developer.

CONTACT

Phone: 506-531-8340

Mail: minhkhoi3105@yahoo.com

EXPERIENCE

2020

VOLUNTEER - MAINTENANCE WORKER

RODGERS APARTMENT RENTALS INC. (IN CANADA) 09/2020-12/2020

- + Rodgers Apartment Rentals provides Moncton and Riverview with safe, clean, and well-kept apartment rentals
- + Task: Fixing and Repair Broken Facilities

2019

SHOES WORKER

FUGASHIN SHOEMAKER COMPANY (IN VIETNAM) 06/2019-08/2019

- + Fugashin is a company making leather shoes and luxury leather accessories
- + Cleaning machines and painting shoes.

EDUCATION

HIGHSCHOOL DIPLOMA

MONCTON HIGH SCHOOL. GPA: 92/100 | 08/2018-06/2020

WEB AND MOBILE APP DEVELOPMENT

NEW BRUNSWICK COMMUNITY COLLEGE (NBCC). 2ND-YEAR STUDENT | 09/2020-Present

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH

Full Professional Proficiency

VIETNAMESE

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

SKILLS

HTML5	CSS3
JavaScript	C#
SQL	Node.js
Angular	ASP.NET MVC
	_
N-tier	Java